给你
Here you go.
希望你好好享受这顿晚饭 还有我的表演
And I hope you enjoyed dinner and the show.
就是我假装我在这里当服务员很开心
The show being me pretending I'm happy as a waitress.
Caroline Max在哪?
Caroline, where is Max?
我已经把十八层地狱都翻了个遍
And I've already checked the bowels of hell.
是啊 我知道我在什么鬼地方工作
Yeah, I know where I work.
Max今天得迟到了
Max is going to be late today
因为她被困在地铁上了
'cause she got stuck on the subway.
但昨天你也说她迟到
But you said yesterday she was late
是因为她被困在地铁上了
because she was stuck on the subway.
不对吧 我记得我昨天说的是她被卡在地铁轮子下面了
No, I believe I said yesterday she got stuck under the subway.
Oleg 来帮帮忙
Oleg, a little help.
哦 你说Max?
Oh, Max?
她今天被困在公交车上了
Today she got stuck on a bus.
你前天也这么说
And you said that the day before yesterday.
- Earl?  - 她被困在月亮
- Earl?  - She got stuck between the moon
和纽约市的中间了
and New York City.
我知道这有点疯狂 不过这是真事
I know it's crazy, but it's true.
对不起我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
我找不到我们的猫Nancy了
I couldn't find our cat, Nancy.
我还被困在公交车上 或者是卡在地铁轮子下面了
Also, I was stuck on the bus or under the subway.
如果他们说的和我的不一样
Unless they told you something different,
那以他们的为准
then I was doing that.
哦 拜托 那个借口
Oh, come on. That excuse was less satisfying
比"系列"广播剧结束还糟
than the end of Serial.
Max 说真的 你到底是怎么对我的?
Max, really, what do you take me for?
嗯 我知道我不能怎么对你
Well, I know where I can't take you.
我不能带你去迪士尼乐园玩
On the big rides at Disneyland.
Nancy还没有回家
Nancy still hasn't come home.
我要疯掉了
I'm freaking out.
我这辈子只爱她一个
She's the only thing I love.
管他呢
Whatever.
我以前也有一只猫 他很酷
I had a cat once. He was cool.
他是黑色的 而且非常性活跃
He was black and very sexually active.
哦 等等 我说的这只酷猫就是我
Oh, wait, the cool cat I'm talking about was me.
Earl 小心点 你这把年纪了 性爱会要你命
Earl, be careful, at your age, you could die having sex.
我知道
I know.
那些女人根本就不会知道我是射了还是泄了
Those ladies don't know whether I'm coming or going.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫
翻译: 段子王小黄  morning  奥利奥  落寞卷菜
校对: 桃茜茜
我觉得Nancy可能再也不会回来了
I think Nancy might be gone for good.
我就是无法相信她竟然没带我一起走
I just can't believe she didn't take me with her.
我们都约好了
We had a deal.
Max 就算她不想回来
Max, she'll come back to the apartment,
她也会来的
even if she doesn't want to.
我是说 我就是这样的
I mean, I always do.
我完全不讶异于你的淡定
I am not surprised you're not worried.
你一直都不怎么喜欢Nancy
You never really liked Nancy.
你总是叫她"那只猫"
You call her "that cat."
还说"那只猫"在我枕头上撒尿了
As in, "that cat" peed on my pillow.
就在我睡觉的时候 Max
While I was sleeping on it, Max.
好吧 怪我咯 我让她喝醉的
Well, blame me. I got her drunk.
嘿 大家好!
Hey, everybody!
姑娘们 你们那玩意儿在我包里
Look, girls, I got your pussy in my purse.
她要么指的是猫 要不然你们两个人就得
Either that's a cat, or you two got to keep better track
找找自己的器官了
of your belongings.
耶!
Yay!
那只猫回来了
That cat's back.
看到了吧 Max?
See, Max?
我很激动
I am excited.
哦 我想死你了
Oh, I missed you so much.
是啊 是啊
Oh, yes, I did.
那不是Nancy
That's not Nancy.
这是只公的
That is a boy.
好吧 Max 对不起 我没有第一时间
Well, Max, sorry I don't check out a cat's junk
就去检查那只猫的器官
the second it comes through the door.
是啊 你只看脸
Yeah, you only look at the face.
这就是我们俩的差异所在
That's the difference between you and me.
你看 这个名牌上写着"小肉桂"
See, look, the name tag says "Cinnamon."
怪不得那个小女孩一直在哭个不停 还说
No wonder that little girl kept crying and saying,
"把肉桂给我 把肉桂给我"
"Give me Cinnamon, Give me Cinnamon."
我看着她的眼睛说
I looked her right in the eye and I said,
"人家包里没有携带香料"
"I don't carry spices in my purse."
Max 你完全反应过度了
Max, you are completely overreacting.
- 这只是...  - 哦! 只是什么?
- It's just a...  - Oh! Just a what?
说啊!
Say it!
只是一只猫啊
It's just a cat.
你!
You!
嘿 它的名牌还是我花了一块钱给它弄的
Hey, I'm the one who fronted us that dollar to get her name tag.
多亏了我 会有人把她捡起来
Thanks to me, someone's gonna pick her up,
看着她 然后说 "哦 你一定是迷路了
look at it, and say, "Oh, you must be lost,
小...猫"
little... cat."
Nancy! 她叫Nancy!
Nancy! Her name's Nancy!
我知道她叫什么!
I know her name!
我只是暂时想不起来了
It got momentarily pushed out of my head
因为我们还有1600件纸杯蛋糕T恤衫
to make room for those 1,600 cupcake T-shirts
卖不掉 而且付不起
we can't unload or pay for.
你以为我没有几乎每天晚上
You think I don't wake up screaming
都为了这些T恤衫尖叫着醒过来吗?
four or five nights a week about those T-shirts?
但是我知道我们的猫叫什么
But I know our cat's name.
你才不会半夜醒来呢
You don't wake up at night ever.
当然不会 我睡得和死婴一样熟 这是我的天赋
No, I sleep like a dead baby, it's my one gift.
哦 电话!
Oh, the phone!
未知号码 可能就是它了!
Unknown number. This could be it!
我喜欢未知来电 正如不知啥时过期的避孕套
I like my numbers like my condom expiration dates, unknown.
你好?
Hello?
- 怎么了?  - 是谁啊 Max?
- Yes?  - Who is it, Max?
她在你手上? 耶!
You have her? Yay!
哦 好的 太棒了
Oh, sure, great.
- 谢谢  - 她在他手上?
- Thank you.  - He has her?
Nancy在他那里?
He has Nancy?
算了吧 晚了
Please, too little, too late.
Max 我们欠债一万美元
Max, we're in $10,000 worth of debt
你还花钱去买新的猫砂?
and you spent money on new kitty litter?
放松点 我也要在里面撒尿的
Relax, I'm going to pee in it, too.
好吧 我猜它比你在你房间里用的
Well, I guess it beats that Sprite bottle
那个雪碧瓶好多了
you've been using in your bedroom.
从房间走到厕所太远了
It's just such a long walk to the bathroom
我每次走的时候
that every time I have to go,
都感觉像是在为多发性硬化症筹钱
it's like I'm raising money for MS.
哦 好消息
Oh, I have good news.
我在这个猫砂盒里找到你丢失的胸罩
I found your lost bra in the litter box.
别以为我还会再穿了
Don't think I'm not still wearing it.
为什么不呢?
I mean, why not?
我还曾吃过一条被车碾过的热呢
I ate a hot dog that rolled under a car the other day.
我还在这里留下了几块土
I left a couple of big clumps in,
让你穿得更自信一点
just to help you out a little.
哦 好的 Nancy来了
Oh, okay, that's Nancy.
这是你们两个重新开始的机会
Here's a chance for a fresh start for you two.
别提那个胸罩 我不知道它为什么想要
And don't bring up the bra, we don't know why she wanted it,
但是它肯定有自己的理由
but I'm sure she had her reasons.
好的 我会好好表现的
Fine, I'll be on my best behavior.
但你得看看它是怎么对我的
But you watch and see how she treats me.
这是双向的
It's a two-way street.
你好 你们的猫在我手里
Hi, I have your cat.
而且你们的门把手也在我手里
And surprisingly, your doorknob.
哦 那个口香糖已经没用了?
Oh, that gum wore out already?
你好啊小兄弟!
Hi, buddy!
你好 我叫Caroline 这位是Max
Hi, I'm Caroline. This is Max.
多谢你帮我们找到...
Thank you so much for bringing back...
- Nancy!  - 我知道!
- Nancy!  - I know!
还有别忘了 它都没正眼看过我
And please note, she did not even look at me.
嗨 我是欧文
Hi. I'm Owen.
我们"欧"你一份人情啊
Well, we are "Owen" you a big thank-you.
我们最近有点缺钱 请问你愿意
Kind of low on cash, how would you feel
买一千件可爱的"纸杯蛋糕"T恤吗?
about 1,000 cute cupcake tees?
我不需要一千件粉红衣裳
Yeah, I don't need 1,000 pink T-shirts.
我不关注体育就已经惹我爸不高兴了
My dad's already mad at me I don't care about sports.
怎么打开这玩意?
How do you get this thing open?
我们一般带Nancy出去
We usually just take Nancy around
是装在旧的吸尘器袋子里
in an old vacuum cleaner bag.
同时也用于我的外出包包
Also doubles as my "going out" purse.
不好意思 可以借过吗?
Pardon me, may I get past?
这种礼仪
Oh, manners.
出现在我家门前?
In our doorway?
我都不知所措了
I don't know what to do.
接下来会出现没有随意丢弃吸毒针头的门廊吗?
What's next, a front stoop with no discarded heroin needles?
我刚从那走上去的
Yeah, I just came up there.
不是今天
Not today.
让我帮你吧
Here, let me help.
我就是一个花了两千块买个装猫袋的傻瓜
I mean, I'm the dumb one who paid $2,000 for a cat carrier.
我怀念自己曾经也这么傻
Hmm. I miss being that stupid.
我的猫也打不开这袋子
You know, my cat can't get this open either.
肯定是没有拇指的缘故
It must be the lack of thumbs.
猫一般只有四个指头 拇指退化了
大清早的遇到个穿西装的"高富帅"?
Rich, funny, and in a suit at 9:00 A.M.?
我真不知所措了
I really don't know what to do.
我的猫 狄更斯 喜欢你的猫
You know, my cat, Dickens, loves your cat.
狄更斯 跟那作家同名?
Oh, Dickens, after the author?
查尔斯·狄更斯 英国作家 代表作"雾都孤儿"
狄更斯著作名为"圣诞颂歌"
狄更斯 跟大作家同名 Max
Dickens, after the author, Max.
我知道他是谁
Yeah, I know who that is.
写了"木偶圣诞颂歌"的那家伙
The guy who wrote Muppets Christmas Carol.
好了 就知道我打得开
There. I knew I'd get it.
因为我有拇指
'Cause I have thumbs.
它在这呢
Oh, there she is.
从养猫来看 你是单身?
So I take it by the cat, you're single?
再单不过了
Big time.
那你就和"狄更斯"住一起吗?
So, do you and Dickens live alone?
糟了 她打算要调情
Oh no, she's trying to flirt.
我经常因工作出差
I travel a lot for work.
我是个风险资本家
I'm a venture capitalist.
所以你也了解情况
So you know how it is.
我了解 非常了解
Oh, I do. I absolutely do.
- 我...  - 要炫耀了
- I...  - Here it comes.
- 我上了沃顿商学院  - 砰
- Went to Wharton.  - Boom.
要是再找不到它 你知道去哪找
Well, if she gets lost again, you know where to find her.
最近几个月 它每天都在
She's been hanging around outside our window
我们窗外转悠
every day for the last couple of months.
所以我放它进来了 希望没事
So I let her in. I hope that's okay.
哪是没事? 简直棒极了
Is that okay? It's awesome.
我希望你女朋友不会介意
I hope your girlfriend didn't mind.
我们刚分手
We just broke up.
所以我是单身
So I'm single.
我得离开了
And I better get going.
我10点要开会
I've got a 10:00 meeting.
Max 把箱子还他
Max, give the man his case.
他10点要开会
He has a 10:00 meeting.
它不想离开这舒适的地方
She doesn't want to get out of cushy this thing.
我完全理解
I totally get it.
我在布鲁克斯东坐按摩椅的时候
I had to be dragged out of that massage chair
得让保安把我拽下来
at Brookstone by mall security.
这是我的名片 如果你想让我过来拿箱子
Well, here's my card, just give me a call
打电话告诉我一声
when you want me to pick up the case.
你有名片?
You have a card?
名片 开会 西装 笑话?
A card, a meeting, a suit, a joke?
你是下一个"白马王子"吗?
Are you the next bachelor?
谢谢你了欧文·查尔斯·博伊德
Well, thank you, Owen Charles Boyd,
帮我们找到我们心爱的...
for bringing back our beloved...
- 它叫Nancy!  - 我知道它的名字
- Her name's Nancy!  - I know her name.
有必要说那么快吗?
Why do I have to say it so fast?
她开玩笑的 只是没你这么风趣
She's joking, she's just not as funny as you.
很高兴见到你
Well, it was nice to meet you.
拜拜 Nancy
Bye, Nancy.
好吧
Okay.
我是在调情
Yes, I was flirting.
但是在为咱们的生意着想
But I was doing it for our business.
你真应该为你自己的"生意"着想
You should really be doing it for your business.
因为你的"生意"就要"失业"了
'Cause your business is going out of business.
他有名片
He has a card.
而且还不是卖药用大麻的
And it's not for medical marijuana.
他是个风险资本家
He's a venture capitalist.
是个能帮我们
That's the kind of fat cat
站稳脚步的"大款"
that can help us get back on our feet.
说起"傍大款" Nancy看起来
Speaking of fat cats, Nancy's looking like
要给Jenny打个电话
she might need to give Jenny a call.
嘿 姐妹们
Hey, girls.
你们找到Nancy了
Oh, you found Nancy.
我就知道它会怀胎而归
I knew she'd come back pregnant.
等等 Sophie 你怎么知道它是怀孕了
Wait, Sophie, how can you tell she's pregnant
而不是像乔纳·希尔那样与发福抗争
and just not fighting the same battle Jonah Hill is fighting?
它的毛发增粗了 双眼炯炯有神
Well, her fur is thicker, she's got a little sparkle in her eye,
还有只小猫咪要从它屁屁探出头来
and there's a little kitten head about to pop out of her patoot.
拜托 用力 Nancy
Come on. Push, Nancy.
别这样 我们都知道你干的好事
Come on, we all know what you did.
现在可不是害臊的时候
Now is not the time to be shy.
你知道你在做什么 对吧 Sophie?
You do know what you're doing, right, Sophie?
这不会像上次你跟我们说的
This isn't like the time you told us
你能用蜡烛自制脱毛蜡那样?
you could do your own bikini wax with a candle?
因为我还留着 上次那香草味伤疤呢
'Cause I still have the vanilla-scented scars from that.
别担心
Don't worry.
在我村子里 所有库金斯基女人
In my village, all the Kuchenskis women
都给动物当产婆
acted as animal midwives.
那是钓汉子的最佳方式
It was the best way to meet guys.
快点 姐妹们
Strap in, girls.
啊! 它要生了!
Ah! She's crowning!
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
我还以为Nancy会聪明点
I thought Nancy was smarter than this.
结果跟我家其他女人
But it turns out she's just like the rest of the women
一个样
in my family.
被垃圾堆边遇到的陌生人搞大肚子
Screwed by some stranger she met in the dumpster.
好了 要生了
Okay, here we go.
哦 这下戒指丢了
Oh, there goes my ring.
我... 抱歉 Nancy
I... sorry, Nancy.
哦 要生了!
Oh, here we go!
快点 姐妹们 我需要一盆热水和干净的毛巾
Come on, girls, I need some hot water and fresh towels.
这些我们都需要 想要了四年
We do, too. For, like, four years.
呃...
Uh...
用这些T恤怎么样?
how about some of these T-shirts?
有何不可呢?
Oh, sure why not use those?
它们曾是我们的美好未来
They used to be our bright future.
现在就只是擦猫崽子的清洁布
Now just a ShamWow for illegitimate cats.
天啊 那声音一定是
Oh, my God, that must be the sound
猫的子宫在"求饶"
of a surrendering cat uterus.
这也算这么久来 第一次有子宫在那床上
Well, it's the first time a uterus has surrendered
"求饶"了
in that bed in a while.
我居然还不想吐
I don't know why I'm not throwing up.
等等 要吐了
Oh, wait. I'm starting to.
我这辈子都不吃韩国饺子了
Well, I'm off Korean dumplings for life.
这一只... 这一只不肯出来
This one... this one won't come out.
它就像猫界的奎因·拉蒂法
It's like the Queen Latifah of kittens.
奎因·拉蒂法曾被爆出柜
Sophie 我收到你的短信说 你跟Nancy在床上
Sophie, I got your text that you were in bed with Nancy.
这个Nancy是谁
Who is this Nancy,
我们啥时又开始玩三人行了?
and when did we go back to doing three-ways?
Nancy是只猫
Nancy's a cat.
唔 那我拒绝
Mm, that's a no.
我还是有底线的
I've got to draw the line somewhere.
我听到消息了
Well, I heard the news.
看来你们俩要在30岁前当外婆了
Looks like you two are grandmothers before you're 30.
说不出我有多惊讶
Can't say I'm surprised.
好了 你们问都不用问
Okay, before you even ask,
我不会照付猫产假的工资
I don't pay for cat maternity leave.
这里可不是谷歌
This isn't Google.
这里连"问杰"都不是 Han
This isn't even Ask Jeeves, Han.
一种人工操作目录索引的美国著名搜索引擎
我可以帮你们 给猫咪们找个好住处
Well, I can help you get the kittens good homes.
我楼里的居民都非常友好
The people in my building are very nice.
但如果是你忘记回收一个泡苹果酒的瓶子
Except if you don't recycle one bottle of sparkling cider,
那你在电梯里 没人会跟你说话
then nobody talks to you in the elevator.
Han 我们不打算把猫咪送走
Han, we're not giving the kittens away.
Nancy让自己成了一只富裕的猫
Nancy landed herself a rich cat,
我们打算靠巨额的猫咪赡养费维生
we're gonna be living off a hefty kitty support.
只有你们俩会绝望到
Only you two would be desperate enough
想找一只招财猫
to try and find a sugar catty.
欧文给你回电话了吗?
So has Owen called you back yet?
呃 我们在博弈呢
Um, we're trading.
"我们在博弈"?
"We're trading"?
"我们在博弈"是单身白人女孩的说法
"We're trading" is lonely white girl talk
意思是"他没给我回电话"
for "he hasn't called me back."
我真是不敢相信 他是个不负责任的爹
I can't believe this. He's a deadbeat dad.
Max 他只是忙
Max, he's just busy.
我觉得你也许是在投射个人情绪
And I think you might be projecting a little
因为你爸爸的缘故
because of your dad.
而我不是治疗专家
Not that I'm a therapist.
因为我连心理咨询用的长沙发都买不起
I mean, I can't even afford a couch.
我这不叫投射
I'm not projecting.
我最拿手识别不负责任的爸爸了!
I just know a deadbeat dad when I don't see one!
他的名片在哪儿?
Where's his card?
我不记得放在哪儿...
I don't remember where I...
Max 放手! 我来搞定这事
Max, let go! I've got this.
那个人真的能帮到我们的生意
That guy can really help us with our business.
拜托 让我来处理吧
Please, let me handle this.
看 瑞恩·高斯林
Look, Ryan Gosling.
- 我来  - 我来
- I got this.  - I got this.
继续 姑娘们 我快要高潮了
Keep going, girls, I'm almost there.
我来 Max
I got this, Max.
等他来拿猫笼的时候
And when he comes to get the cat carrier,
我会跟他说
I'll talk to him.
你太容易激动了
You're way too emotional.
你连我的围裙都下手了
You just went to third base with my apron.
坐在这台阶上也挺好的
Sitting on this stoop is nice.
我们怎么就一直没来这里坐坐呢?
How come we never sit out here?
这就是原因
There it is.
拜托 只是Rico而已
Oh, please, it's just Rico.
Rico看起来不错 我想他又多了个纹身
Rico looks good. I think he got another tattoo.
听着 欧文到这儿的时候 我们应该还活着
Look, when Owen gets here, should we still be alive,
请让我来进行谈话
please let me do the talking.
猫咪的事先放一边 欧文可以帮我们
Kittens aside, Owen can help us.
一个风险投资人会买多家公司
A venture capitalist buys companies
还能让它们起死回生
and turns them around.
拜托 我看过"风月俏佳人"(电影)
Yeah, I've seen Pretty Woman.
那让我意识到 我的收费还不够高
That's how I realized I wasn't charging enough.
走 Max 他来了
Go, Max, here he comes.
好的 但我会在窗户里面看着
All right, but I'll be watching inside from the window.
这样可能更好 因为我不放心Nancy独自
It's probably better, because I don't trust Nancy alone
和其他猫在一起
with those kittens.
她有一些严重的产后症状
She's got some serious postpartum.
我离开房间后 她曾用一只颤抖的爪子
When I left the room, she was lighting a Menthol 100
点燃了薄荷油
with a shaky paw.
嗨
Hi.
我们居然能够活着走向彼此
Crazy we live walking distance from each other.
不是的 是"优步"司机
We don't. The Uber driver
不愿意经过拐角处的消防栓
wouldn't go past the fire hydrant on the corner.
挂着只血淋淋的鞋子的那个吗?
The one with the bloody shoe hanging from it?
没错
That's the one.
那什么... 我就是来拿那个箱子的
You know what? I'm just gonna take the cat carrier.
在你走之前...
Before you go...
我们有个小型的纸杯蛋糕公司
we have this small cupcake company
希望成为一家大企业
that's just begging to be an empire,
我想跟你讨教下 生意上的一些事
and I wanted to pick your brain about some business stuff.
猫 钱 婊子
好吧 你的狄更斯让我们的猫怀孕了
Okay, so your Dickens got our cat pregnant,
而它刚刚生了五只猫咪
and she just had five kittens.
以它的年龄 我们不用付钱做体外手术
And at her age, it's a miracle we didn't have to pay
真是个奇迹
for in vitro.
你怎么知道是狄更斯的孩子?
How do you know they are Dickens's?
我不是说Nancy很随便
I'm not saying that Nancy's easy,
只是 我看见它进进出出
it's just, I've seen her go in and out
很多窗户
of a lot of windows.
他刚刚掉了一把枪?
Did he just drop a gun?
没事 他还有很多
It's fine. He has more.
好吧 给我助理打电话 你可以跟我讨教
Okay, call my assistant, you can pick my brain.
我只是不想在人行道边聊
I just don't want it to be off the sidewalk.
真的 我得走了 我不能死
Really, I got to go. I can't get killed.
我穿的是新款的绒面革乐福鞋
I'm wearing new suede loafers.
"优步" 助理 绒面革乐福鞋?
Uber, an assistant, and suede loafers?
你是真实的吗?
Are you for real?
希望我没有打扰你
I hope I'm not intruding.
没有 请进
No, come in.
我刚刚在刷我的新乐福鞋
I was just brushing my new loafers.
我买这双鞋 当作是给自己的分手礼物
I bought them as a break-up gift for myself.
与我前女友不一样的是 我能填满它
But unlike my ex-girlfriend, these have a sole.
我不想跟你的助理提猫的事
I didn't wanna mention the cat situation to your assistant.
你知道的 接下来整个食堂就会议论
Next thing you know, it's all over the lunch room:
欧文·查尔斯·博伊德的猫很滥交
Owen Charles Boyd's cat is a raw-dogger.
被我的生意伙伴给踩了一脚
My business partner stepped on them.
说那是个意外
Said it was an accident.
感觉不像
Didn't feel like one.
一只鞋有可能 但两只?
One shoe yes, but both?
非常不可能
Highly unlikely.
欧文 有时候在生活中 不仅仅是一只
Owen, sometimes in life, it's not just an innocent cat
无辜的猫被操蛋了
that gets screwed.
一个姑娘也会被操蛋
A girl can get screwed as well.
哦 你好 有什么事吗?
Oh, hey, hi. What's happening?
比如 被一个错误的商业决策给毁了
As in, screwed by one bad business decision.
我的合作伙伴Max 还有我
My partner, Max, and I recently invested
最近把我们的所有积蓄投资到... 这里 看看
all our savings in... well, here, take a look.
哦 我的咖啡!
Oh, my coffee!
- 哦  - 我的乐福鞋!
- Oh.  - My loafer!
我的咖啡洒在我的乐福鞋上了!
My coffee's on my loafer!
让我来
Here, let me.
不 轻轻擦 不能猛擦绒面革
No, you dab. You don't wipe suede.
轻轻擦
You dab.
轻轻擦 轻轻擦 抱歉
Dab. Dab. I'm sorry.
我从前懂的
I used to know that.
这是富人必修课
That's Rich 101.
我去弄点水
Let me just go find some water
然后轻轻擦它 不会猛擦它
and I'll dab, not wipe, this out.
我们还没聊完 我会回去的
We're not done yet. I'm going back in.
进行得非常顺利
It's going really well though.
哪儿有水?
Where's water?
你知道怎么撤回邮件吗?
Do you know how to unsend an email?
要是我知道 我那有钱的前男友就不会发现
If I did, my rich ex-boyfriend would've never found out
我嫌弃他口齿不清
what I thought of his lisp
我现在也就会住在法阔蓝部了
and I'd be living in the "thouth of Franth" right now.
他在哪?
Where is he?
他得见见这些可爱的小混蛋
He needs to see these adorable bastards.
Max 你怎么知道我在这儿?
Max, how did you find me here?
我跟你说 我正在进行一场思维漫步
I told you I was going on a "think walk."
我跟踪了你
I followed you.
我以前都没发现你喜欢在商店玻璃前
I never noticed how much you check yourself out
照镜子 你这是毛病
in store windows. You have a problem.
你们知道怎么把 "自私透顶的蠢猪"
Do either of you know a way to turn the phrase,
变成赞美之词么
"self-absorbed, ridiculous pig" into a compliment?
如果我会的话 我就能上"飞黄腾达"这节目了
If I did, I'd still be on The Apprentice.
欧文马上就能看到这封邮件了
Owen's going to see that email
我要被炒了
and I'm going to get fired.
我必须得学着注意细节了
I have to start paying attention to details.
我要进去了
I'm just gonna go back in.
什么? 我才不在乎呢
What? I don't care.
要是不让我进去 你也休想进去
Not without me you're not.
Max 求你了 让我来处理吧
Max, please, let me handle this.
我求你了
I'm begging you.
我们马上就能成功了 看 我已经拿到他的鞋了
We're getting close, look, I'm holding his shoe.
如果他不拿出点行动来
If he doesn't step up here,
这些小猫就会觉得被忽视了
these kittens will feel neglected,
然后它们迟早会成为服务员
and it is only a matter of time
或者比这更糟
till they are waitressing or worse.
Max 你错了
Max, you're wrong.
没有什么比服务员更糟的了
There's nothing worse than waitressing.
Max 冷静!
Max, stop!
你会把一切都搞砸的
You'll ruin everything.
我能搞定这事 拯救咱们
I can fix this and us.
我们没救了
We are beyond help.
是要帮这些小猫
It's all about these kittens.
- 现在 闪开 我来处理  - 不 我来
- Now move, I got this. - No, I got this.
- 我来  - 我来
- I got this. - I got this.
我...
I...
噢 天呐
Oh, my God.
发生了什么?
What the hell is happening?
没错 我带着一篮子的小猫来到你的办公室
That's right. I came to your office with a basket of cats.
Max 不好意思
Max, I'm so sorry.
嗯哼 他才是那个应该觉得抱歉的家伙
Yeah, well, he's the one who should be sorry.
我要你看着这些小公猫
I want you to look these kittens in the whiskers
告诉他们狄更斯不是他们的父亲
and tell them that Dickens is not their father.
你凭什么觉得他们是我家的 凭什么?
What makes you think they're mine. Why?
就因为他们长得
Because they look just like Dickens
跟狄更斯小时候一模一样吗
when he was a tiny baby kitten.
噢 这只更可爱了
Oh, and this one's even cuter.
还有那一只
And that one.
我会照顾他们的
I'll take them all.
除了那一只 看起来有点傻
But not that one. Seems a little off.
不像别的那么机灵
Not quite as alert as the others.
噢 她配不上你吗?
Oh, she's not good enough for you?
- Max 你在感情投射了  - 我没有
- Max. Projecting.  - I'm not projecting.
他说她配不上他
He said she's not good enough for him.
什么?
What?
就因为她是意外怀孕所生 而且数学不好吗?
Just because she was unplanned and not good at math?
或者是因为胸部发育的太早?
Developed boobs way too early?
好吧 我是在感情投射
Okay, fine. I'm projecting.
发生了什么?
What is going on?
Caroline 我们不是准备上床吗?
Caroline, are we gonna hook up or what?
这或许是 最奇怪的前戏了
This is, like the weirdest foreplay ever.
上床? 你凭什么认为我想跟你上床?
Hook up? What would make you think I want to hook up?
噢 因为我的商业调情?
Oh, because I business flirted?
这是沃顿必修课
That's Wharton 101.
这可不仅仅是商业调情
It was more than business flirting.
你哀求着要来我的办公室
You begged to come to my office,
穿着透视装出现在我面前
show up wearing a see-through shirt.
这是因为我没别的衣服可穿了
That was not by choice.
便宜货都这样
It is cheaply made.
我过来是想跟你谈生意的
I came here to talk to you about our business,
让你能给我们投资 哪怕就一点点也是好的...
and possibly get you to invest in a small, but spirited...
投资? 这可是世界金融中心
Invest? This is the financial capital of the world.
是 没错
Yes, it is.
为什么我要去投资一个快倒闭的小蛋糕店?
Why would I invest in a desperate little cupcake shop?
你!
You!
够了!
That's it!
不许你收养小猫了
No cats for you.
你知道吗?
You know what?
你真是一个自私透顶的蠢猪
You are a self-absorbed, ridiculous pig.
你随便说
Says you.
你的秘书也这么认为
And your assistant.
查收邮件吧
Check your email.
我刚把邮件撤回了
I was able to unsend it.
耶!
Yay!
好吧 或许你还会想重新点击发送
Yeah, might want to re-ignite that LinkedIn profile.
你应该常常一个人在家吧 需要一只小猫吗?
You're gonna be home a lot more, you want a cat?
Han 谢谢你照顾这些小猫
Thanks for taking the kittens, Han.
我觉得你对小动物都很有同情心
I feel like you have an understanding
因为你自己就是
of small creatures, being one yourself.
放心吧 我公寓里都是女同
Have no fear, my building is loaded with lesbians.
她们收养小猫的速度
They take home rescue cats
远远快于收养同性恋
faster than they take home other lesbians.
好的 现在让我们讨论下我的收养条款吧
Okay, let's discuss my terms.
与我那些非人类的孩子相比
Unlike all my non-animal children,
我希望它们能得到悉心的照顾
I want to know they're taken care of.
你们难道不了解女同吗?
What part of lesbian don't you understand?
夜晚来临的时候 她们甚至会用法兰绒把小猫包好的
They'll be swaddled in a flannel shirt by nightfall.
好的 这只名为瘾君子
Okay, now this one, I call Junkie.
因为它痴迷于猫薄荷
'Cause he's got a serious Catnip problem.
噢 所以你在一周之内就培养了一名吸毒爱好者
Oh, so you raised a drug addict within a week.
不错嘛
Sounds about right.
这两只应该在一起
These two should try and stay together.
我们叫他们 权力的游戏第一部
We call them Game of Thrones One
和权力的游戏第二部
and Game of Thrones Two.
因为他们是兄妹又是恋人
'Cause they're siblings and lovers.
这只是公的
This one's the boy.
看看他 跟他学学怎么性交
Watch him and learn what humping looks like.
这只超级温柔
This one's pretty bland.
她总是趴着 也不叫
She lays around, doesn't meow much,
当它叫唤起来像是电话响个不停
and when she does, she's kind of phoning it in.
我们管她叫艾米·亚当斯
We call her Amy Adams.
没错
Yep.
最后一只要格外注意了
This last one gets special attention.
虽然她最小了 但是很有潜力
She's the smallest, but she's got potential.
我是说 看看这些乳头
I mean, look at those nipples.
现在我满脑子都是乳头了
And now the nipples are all I see.
祝你好运
Have a nice life.
我会上图片分享网看你们的
I'll find you on Instagram.
还有看看"暴躁猫"
Check out Grumpy Cat.
跟他学学
Do what he does.
那么 再见了 小猫咪们
Well, bye, kitties.
记着 脱衣舞不是舞蹈
And remember, stripping isn't dancing.
现在我满脑子都是它们穿着胸贴的样子了
And now all I can see is them wearing pasties.
你知道吗 Max?
You know what, Max?
我们不需要那个有钱人来帮我们
We don't need that rich guy to fix our business.
我们可以靠自己
We can do it ourselves.
我在骗谁呢? 我们的生意还不如
Who am I kidding? Our business is in worse shape
高尔夫球场手推车的老头呢
than two retired guys in a golf cart.
你知道咱们得先修理什么吗?
Well, you know what we'd better fix?
就是Nancy
Nancy.
有钱人说的没错 她就是个荡妇
'Cause he was right, she's a slut.
有人发现她正在小巷里和一只虎斑猫玩69式
Someone just found her 69-ing a tabby in the alley.